《僵尸国度》前情提要
Previously on Z Nation.
哇哦 是个活生生的婴儿
Whoa. It's a real live baby.
别抱得像是抱个活生生的手榴弹
Don't hold him like he's a live grenade.
我跟婴儿并没有那么亲近
Me and babies, not so much.
我们在执行一个至关重要的任务
We're on a high priority mission
要把这个人护送到加州的疾控中心
to get this man to a CDC lab in California.
一些衣衫褴褛的烂平民群体不得不引起担忧
Can't worry about some raggedy ass group of civilians.
我们并不是什么衣衫褴褛的烂平民群体 长官
Nothing raggedy ass about this group of civilians, sir.
放松点
Relax.
加内特和沃伦知道他们在做什么
Garnett and Warren know what they're doing.
伊利诺斯州南部
来 给
There you are.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Ah, thank you, honey.
恩恩 没什么比早上来一杯咖啡更好了
Mmmm-mmm. Nothing like the first cup.
我跟你的止痛药
I will see your vicodin
再加一颗四环素
and raise you one tetracycline.
叫牌
Call.
3个K
Three of a kind.
满堂红
Full house.
A最大咯
Aces high.
老兄
Man.
你已经连赢五把了
That's five hands in a row.
如果你还想继续用我的桌子
If you're gonna continue to use my deck
那你就别再从屁股里掏牌了
you need to quit pulling cards out your ass.
噢 哟哟
- Oh boo hoo. -
嘿 嘘  等下 市民Z回线上了
Hey shhh. Hold on, he's back on.
小伙伴们 我想说的是 恶劣天气马上来袭
Friends, I'm talking about mean weather coming in fast.
有报道说是龙卷风
Some reports of tornados.
找到庇护所快躲躲
Find shelter and take cover.
在外面很危险 比往常来说更危险
It's dangerous out there. More so than usual.
现在我为大家放一曲灾难前暖心的歌曲听听吧
Now back to the soothing sounds of the Apocalypse.
你知道吗 在他搞错了直升机的事儿后
You know after he was so wrong about that chopper
我觉得天气预报的活儿挺适合他
weatherman's a pretty good job for that geek.
轮到你们了
You're up.
没事儿吧
All good?
平静的一夜
Peaceful night.
你的脑残粉说马上会有风暴来袭
Your stalker said there's a storm front coming in.
外面有迹象吗
How is it out there?
乌云满布 也有可能是僵尸来袭
Cloudy with a chance of zombie.
好了 你俩去休息吧
Okay, you two get some rest.
没问题
You got it.
我曾经过过更差的生活
I've had worse days.
这也不能算差吧
It's not a bad set up.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmmm.
你知道吗
You know,
我真的开始觉得这里有点家的感觉了
I'm really starting to feel at home here.
我在考虑在这里搞一个烧烤摊
I'm thinking about putting a barbecue right here.
要先把这东西清理一下
This one needs to be flipped.
我真的很喜欢屋主的这些布景 这些花儿
I really like what they did with the landscaping, the flowers,
所有东西 都特别有家的感觉
everything. So homey.
是啊 只可惜他们都死了
Yeah. Too bad they're dead.
是啊
Yeah.
好
Okay.
对不起 进错房间了
Sorry. Wrong room.
好的
Okay.
我的天 是床  上次我们在床上做是多久之前了
Oh my God. A bed. When was the last time we did it in a bed?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
全裸咩
Naked?
把衣服都脱了
Like no clothes?
一丝不挂好嘛 宝贝儿
Full commando, baby.
我的天  你还真是浪漫
Oh my God, you are such a romantic.
这个
The...
毛毯
blanket...
我只是想
I was just...
对不起
Sorry.
真怕那家伙
Scared of that one.
最好就是甭惹她
Best not to mess.
你知道吗 如果我们好好培养下那两个 僵尸可有的受了
You know if we breed those two, it'd be all over for the zombies
我记不得上次偷偷和别人溜出来是什么时候了
Can't remember the last time I snuck off with somebody.
我根本记不得上一次有这个念头是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time I wanted to.
你仍想着他
You still think about him?
安托万吗
Antoine?
我尽量不去想他
I try not to.
我也不知道后来发生了什么 所以也还好
And I never heard what happened, so there's not much point.
你呢
What about you?
我曾经每天都想艾米和孩子们
I used to think about Amy and the kids everyday.
每当我闭上眼 分别时的场景就历历在目
Every time I closed my eyes, I saw the end all over again.
到了一定程度 我就放弃了
It got to a certain point where I just gave up.
不去在乎我自己是死是活
Didn't care if I lived or died.
有趣的事儿就出现了
And a funny thing happened.
我没死
I didn't die.
那么多事发生了后
And with everything that's happened
记住过去变得越来越难
it's been harder and harder to remember the past.
我想那是件好事儿 不是吗
I guess that's a good thing, right?
但愿吧
Guess so.
我们是不是离你家乡很近
Are we close by your hometown?
我知道你在想什么 答案是 不行
I know what you're thinking, and the answer is no.
我们往西走的时候顺便拜访一下
Just swing by on our way west.
为什么 都已经过去很久了
Why? It's long gone.
他死了
He's gone.
我只希望当时候我能等等他
And I just wish that I would've waited for him
在最后一次出发之前能跟他好好的道别
and said goodbye before the last time I got shipped out.
你不想去确认下吗
Don't you want to know for sure?
你自己都不确定的事 你就没有办法去忘记
You can't start forgetting what you don't know.
这看起来可不妙
That does not look good.
这是龙卷风
It's tornado weather.
龙卷风要来了
That was close.
嘿
Hey,
hey.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
啊 是的
Uh, yeah.
不
No.
不 我知道
No, I dunno.
他们来了
Incoming!
阿猫阿狗们 该走了
Puppies and kittens! Time to go!
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
所有人从后门出去
Everybody out the back!
翻译：小南 香蕉奶昔 冬可可     校对：Jophy
后期：hhjie     时间轴：阿黎     总监：Jophy
我来帮你
I give you mercy.
僵尸
国度
第一季     第五集
北极光基地
国家安全局指挥中心
我讨厌盲点 伙计
I hate blind spots, boy.
让我焦虑啊
Make me anxious.
都消化不良了呢
Mess with my digestion.
真有趣
That was funny.
对不起 我忘了你了
Sorry, I forgot you.
噢 对了 你在戒酒呢
Oh that's right, you're on the wagon.
对不起 我忘了
Sorry, I forgot.
比独饮独酌更惨的就是不能喝酒了
The only thing worse than drinking alone is not drinking.
美女你好啊
Hello, beautiful.
咱们是要找什么
What are we looking at here?
哇哦
Wow.
厉害啊 龙卷风走廊果然名不虚传
Dang. They don't call it Tornado Alley for nothing.
我没喝醉
I am not drunk.
你才喝醉了
You're drunk.
你全家都喝醉了
No, your mom's drunk.
为了持续为您带来
In our continuing effort to bring you
最新消息 我们僵尸电视台调用了
up to the minute information, we at Z-TV have acquired
一颗被弃用多时的
a National Weather Service satellite
气象局卫星信号
that they aren't using anymore.
但这都不是重点
But that's not important.
现在镜头转向南方天气预报员约翰 史密斯
We now go to John Smith, southern weather correspondent
听听他的意见
to get his opinion on the story.
这是我这么多年来见过最强的风暴了
This is the badassest storm this weatherman has ever seen.
从墨西哥湾一直延伸到密西西比河谷
From the Gulf of Mexico right up the Mississippi Valley,
麻烦临头咯
trouble is brewing.
我不知道该叫他飓风还是龙卷风
I don't know if they call this thing a turricane or a tornado
还是别的什么 但是只要你在芝加哥南边
or what. But if you're anywhere south of Chicago
或者落基山东面
or east of the Rockies,
我可得警告你们 赶快躲起来
I'm issuing a get your butt in a bunker warning.
我希望你们几个能听到这个
Hey, I hope you guys are getting this.
安迪和小伙伴们
Addy and friends.
你们得赶紧找地方躲起来
You guys got to seek shelter immediately because
这风暴很厉害 还有
this is bad. And
你们马上去找避难所
when you seek shelter immediately
找到过后
and after you do that,
你们马上联系我告诉我你们的位置
you need to contact me and tell me where you are.
我会告诉你接下来该怎么做 好咩
And I'll update you with further instructions. Okay?
好了 我是市民Z 播报完毕
All right, well this is Citizen Z, and I'm signing off.
谁是安迪
Who's Addy?
接下来我们走哪条路
So which way do we go?
风暴从墨西哥湾向北推进
The storm is pushing north from the gulf.
如果我们能走上70号公路 就可以躲过风暴
If we make it to the I-70, we can outrun it.
这风暴科比破卡车快多了
That storm is going faster than that craptastic truck ever will.
是的 我们不能在大路上走了 你听见市民Z说的了
Yeah, we got to get off the road. You heard Citizen Z.
我们得去找避难所
We got to seek shelter.
我们现在需要做的就是逃离这个鬼地方
What we need is to get the hell out of here.
我可不会因为那个卫星小子说了两句就不走了
I ain't stopping just cuz some punk with a satellite says so.
慢着 我听错了什么吗
Okay, hang on. Am I missing something?
你们大老远把我拽过来
You did not drag my ass this far
可不是为了让龙卷风把救世主吹到天上吧
so that mankind's hope could get sucked up by a tornado,
是吧
did you?
嘿 安迪
Hey, Addy.
你一直不说话
You know you've been quiet.
我只是想确认你是否还好
Just want to make sure you're okay.
恩 我还好
Yeah, I'm fine.
只是
Just,
你知道的 僵尸
you know, zombies.
有谁有薄荷糖吗
Anybody got a mint?
卡斯尔伯恩特 那是你家乡是吧
Castle Point. That's your hometown right?
哇哦 看 风暴来了
Whoa. Look at that storm coming in.
好吧 你赢了
Okay, fine. You win.
欢迎回家 罗伯塔
Welcome home, Roberta.
所以你对这个小镇很熟吗
So you know this town?
我在这里出生长大
Born and raised here.
我们需要避一避
We need to take cover.
这附近有什么安全的地儿吗
Is there someplace safe nearby?
有我家有个防风窖
Yeah, there's a storm cellar in my house.
你家离这有多远
How close by is your house?
不算远
It's not far.
我认识这些人
I knew these people.
我的邻居
My neighbor.
上司
My boss.
我的
My...
是他吗
Is that him?
他是谁
Who's him?
噢 不
Oh, no.
我们不是来找你死去的丈夫的 好吗
No. We are not here searching for dead hubby, are we?
走吧
Let's go.
避难所在这边
Shelter's this way.
快走
Get going.
真绿啊
It's so green.
我从来没见过天空这样
I never seen a sky look like that.
我只在电视上见过龙卷风
I've only seen tornadoes on TV.
我不喜欢龙卷风
I don't like tornadoes.
我想它们也不待见我
I'm pretty sure they don't like me either.
那个吗
That it?
就是那个
That's it.
一万 快来
10K, come on!
快开啊
Come on!
如果他在里面
If he's in there and he's...
我会毫不犹豫的
I will not hesitate.
家有僵尸的感觉真好
Home sweet zombie.
从椅子上滚下来
Get out of that chair!
你快给我滚开
Go on and get out of there!
这是我老公最喜欢的椅子
That's my husband's favorite chair!
好吧
All right.
呃 楼上安全
Uh, upstairs is all good.
让我来
I got this.
请不要开枪
Please don't shoot us.
我丈夫受伤了
My husband is hurt.
你在我家里干什么
What are you doing in my house?
有个消防员说我们在这里会很安全
The fireman said we'd be safe here.
好了
Here we go.
像狂犬一样吠叫吧
Bark like a dog for me.
好吧我刚不是对你说的 不过我很感动
Well I wasn't talking to you, but I'm impressed.
天啊
God.
从三级风暴变成七层地狱了
From a Category Three to the Seventh Circle of Hell.
三角洲X光小队 希望你们大家伙儿不在那片乌云底下
Delta-Xray-Delta, I hope you guys aren't underneath that.
快啊 给我个信号
Come on. Drop me a note.
放个照明弹 给我个电话 什么都行
Send up a flare. Give me a ring.
如果我找不到你们 我是帮不来了你们的
I can't help you if I can't find you.
你会没事的
You're going to be okay.
他是个医生
He's a doctor.
额
Uh,
他们只是这么叫我而已
well they sorta just call me Doc.
不
No.
不需要医生 我只要睡一会儿就好
No doctor. I just... need a nap.
哦内什么 那可不行 老兄
Oh that, no that wouldn't be good, dude.
千万别睡过去
Do not nap.
别让他睡着 他至少是脑震荡了
Don't let him fall asleep. He's got a bad concussion at least.
里克 里克
Rick? Rick?
快救救他
Help him!
地下室安全
Basement's clear.
他不会有事吧
Is he gonna be okay?
是这个消防员吗
Is this the fireman?
什么
What?
是这个消防员带你们来这儿的吗
Is this the fireman that brought you here?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许吧 他当时头上戴着头盔
Maybe. He was wearing a helmet.
可能就是他
Maybe it's him.
我觉得就是他
I think it is.
谢谢
Thank you.
暴风雨来之前 我们要离开这儿
We need to get out of here before this storm hits.
那去哪儿呢 哈
And go where, huh?
那我们怎么办 坐以待毙吗
What are we supposed to do, just sit heres cure.
地下室是安全的 我们可以下去避一避
The basement is secure. We can ride it out down there.
我们只要在暴风雨来之前 找够必须的物资就好
Let's just gather some supplies before it hits.
厨房里有不少必需品呢
Kitchen was pretty well stocked up.
有水和罐头
There's water and canned food.
不过没有医疗用品 也没有电池
No medical supplies, no batteries though.
我们要和外界取得联络
We need to get our communications up.
你们俩 去周围找找看
You two, go out in the neighborhood.
看能找到些什么 但别走远
See what you can find. But don't go far.
一定要在暴风雨来之前赶回来
Be sure to get back before the storm hits.
詹妮 这些人在这里干什么
Janey what are all these people doing here?
我爸妈马上要回家来吃饭了
My parents will be home for dinner any minute.
他能撑过去吗
Is he gonna make it?
你是问真的吗
Is that a serious question?
我不知道
I don't know.
他脑袋上裂了个大窟窿
He got cracked on the dome.
好了 至少我
Okay, I for one
不想和这家伙一起困在地下室里
do not want to be trapped in a basement with this guy
他的大脑要开始尸化了
when he starts craving brains.
别理他
Don't mind him.
他老妈从没好好教他
His mama didn't raise him right.
最好我有药品 或者急救箱
Well if I had the proper meds or a first aid kit...
消防站可能还有急救用品
You know the fire station may still have first aid supplies.
嘿
Hey,
把地下室锁好
lock down the basement.
如果那小子开始尸化 我要你立刻处理掉
If that kid turns, I want you to be right on that.
好的 当然
Yeah, of course.
看好墨菲 暴风雨开始之前我们会回来的
Keep an eye on Murphy. We'll be back before the party starts.
艾迪
Addy!
嘿
Hey!
什么
What?
怎么了
这地方勾起了好多回忆
This place brings back so many memories.
怎么了
What?!
我初吻的地儿
My first kiss.
和那个消防员
With the fireman?
安托万 是的
Antoine, yeah.
当心
Look out!
直到现在我才想起那个初吻
I totally forgot about that kiss until now!
那一定是牛逼的一吻
That must have been some kiss!
那可不仅仅是一个吻
It was more than just a kiss!
那个吻是爱的诠释
It was a kiss that explained things
我们都无法用语言来表达
We couldn't seem to say to each other!
看看你这大情圣
Look who's the big romantic!
我觉得这是你对我讲的第一件私事儿
I think that's the first personal story you ever told me!
我爱他
I loved that boy.
这边走
This way.
看起来很久没人来过了
Doesn't look like anybody's been here for a while.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们看看能找到什么好东西
Let's find what we can and get out of here.
急救箱 看起来不错
First aid kits look good.
没用过的
Hardly touched.
还有些吗啡
Even some morphine.
别跟医生讲哦
Don't tell Doc.
他可能还在这里的哪个地方
You know he could still be around here somewhere.
是啊
Yeah.
两年前的新泽西之战 我把这张照片寄过来的
I sent this after the Battle of New Jersey two years ago.
我们差点就能说当面说再见了
Closest we got to a goodbye.
他执勤那天 我离开了
I deployed while he was on duty.
我应该等他回家的
I should've waited for him to get home.
听着
Look.
肯定有人住过你家里 厨房里有储备
Someone's living in your house. The pantry's stocked.
那小俩口也说见过一个消防员
That couple said they met a fireman.
有可能他还活着
There's a chance he's...
没希望了
That life is gone.
很早之前我就知道了
I've known that for a long time.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
找地方避避 快
Shelter! Now!
选择去留吧
Pick your poison.
里面比外面安全
It's safer in here than out there.
好 你看到他了吗
Okay. Do you see him?
现在我们面对的是一群死人了
It's the living against the dead now.
好吧
All right.
子弹用完了
I'm out.
我也是
Me too.
你后面
Behind you.
安托万
Antoine?
当心
Look out!
安托万
Antoine.
是他吗
Is that him?
不是
No.
是他的最好朋友
No, it's his best friend,
迪尔伯恩
Dearborn.
马特·迪尔伯恩
Matt Dearborn.
给你
Here.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Yeah.
轻点儿
Easy now.
抱歉
Sorry.
跟外面那些兄弟会的小子说 快关掉死亡金属乐 吵死了
Tell those frat boys out there to turn down the death metal.
不然我又要叫警察来了
I'll call the cops again.
我会说的
I'll tell them.
这老兄的大脑在充血 快崩溃了
The dude's brain is getting crushed by the swelling.
我们要想办法降低脑压
We need to relieve the pressure.
好的 我们该怎么做
Great. How we gonna do that?
额 我不知道具体的方法
Uh, I don't know exactly. But...
不过我在一集《急诊室的故事》里看到过
But I saw this once on an episode of ER.
我们要把大脑里的血抽出来 我想
We need to drain the blood out I think.
所以我们要找个尖尖的锋利的东西
So I need something sharp and pointy to...
比如螺丝锥啊 碎冰锥啊什么的
Like a corkscrew, an ice pick?
墨菲
Murphy!
墨菲 来帮帮忙
Murphy? A little help.
我去
Damn it.
墨菲
Murphy!
怎么回事儿 伙计
What the hell, man?
墨菲
Murphy!
全世界都支离破碎了 伙计
The world's coming apart around us, man.
你还有心情做头发
And you decide it's time for a haircut?
不许他靠近里克
Keep him away from Rick!
墨菲 我需要你的帮助
Murphy, I need your help.
找个锋利的东西 我们要切开他的头骨
Find something sharp to penetrate his skull.
要够锋利切开头骨 了解
Sharp enough to penetrate his skull. Got it.
是该把他大卸八块了
About time we piked him.
他在瞎说什么
What is he talking about?!
开玩笑注意场景好吗
Way to read the room!
他在瞎说什么
What is he talking about?
别紧张 没人要把你丈夫大卸八块
Don't, don't worry. Nobody's gonna pike your husband.
艾迪去哪儿了
Where's Addy?
艾迪
Addy!
艾迪 艾迪
Addy? Addy?
怎么了 你怎么回事啊
What, what is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
麦克 我需要你 伙计
Mack! I need you, man!
去吧 好吧
- Go. - All right.
找到了吗 墨菲
How we doin' Murphy?!
谢谢
Thanks.
好了
Okay.
把他牢牢按住
Just hold him still.
好了听着 如果这玩意儿能行的话 会飙很多血出来
Now look, if this works right there could be a lot of blood.
不过那是正常的
But that's good.
飙血是个好现象 因为我们要给他降低脑压
That's a good thing because we want to relieve the pressure.
那样的话 大脑就有空间来
And then that way the brain will have room to...
你还是别看了
Don't watch.
我勒个去
Oh damn.
就知道会这样
I knew this was gonna happen.
噢
Oh...
别看我啊 医生
Don't look at me... doctor.
不是吧 孩子
Jeez, kid.
用来当榔头 榔头
As a hammer. A hammer.
哦
Oh.
那可以
That's good.
哦我天
Oh God.
好吧我猜闹压已经降低了
Well I guess that relieved the pressure.
这能行吗
Is this gonna work?
我也不知道
I don't know.
那一集我也没看完
I didn't see the end of the episode.
他肯定会没事的 我知道的 我知道的
He's gonna be all right. I know it. I know it.
这样 把头压一压
Here. Just apply pressure.
就想这样子
Just like that.
特洛伊
Troy.
文斯
Vince.
麦克
Mike.
还有迪尔伯恩
And Dearborn.
我给予你仁慈
I give you mercy.
愿你们在天堂安息
May God give you peace.
好了吗
You ready?
准备大干一场吧
Let's take it to 'em.
他们都去哪了
Where'd they all go?
我们走吧
Come on. Let's go.
很好
That's good.
可能我该趁他昏迷不醒的时候
Maybe I should've pulled the drill bit
把钻头再往外拔一点的
while he was still knocked out.
罗伯塔
Roberta!
那个东西是不是看起来很可怕
Does that thing look mad to you?
该不会就是
Is that what I think?
他们可不是鲨鱼
They ain't sharks!
老天爷啊 你来真的吗
Really, God?! Really?!
我们得赶紧进去
Now! We got to get inside!
快点 没时间了
Come on! There's no time!
快走
Let's go!
墨菲 把那个僵尸解决了
Murphy, take care of that zombie!
知道了 多克
Get it, Doc!
他怎么样了
How is he?
不太清楚
I don't know.
你都做了些什么
What did you do?
做了一下开颅去骨瓣减压术
Oh, decompressive craniectomy.
我在他头顶上插了根钻头进去
I put a drill to the dome.
噢
Oh.
一万和卡桑卓呢
Where's 10K and Cassandra?
我也不太清楚
I don't know.
沃伦
Warren!
墨菲 你在干什么
Murphy! What are you doing?!
赶快刺死那个东西
Pike that thing now!
我们回不去了 找个地方躲躲
We're not gonna make it back! Take shelter!
去车里面
Run for the car!
罗伯塔
Roberta!
罗伯塔 你在干什么
Roberta! What are you doing?!
罗伯塔 听见我说话了吗
Roberta! Can you hear me?!
求你别这样
Please don't do this!
你在干什么
What are you doing?
风暴马上要来了
The storm's gonna come any second!
赶快出来
Come on! Hurry up!
赶紧的 罗伯塔
Come on, Roberta!
罗伯塔 你到底在干嘛 罗伯塔 把门打开
Roberta! What are you doing, Roberta?! Open the door!
麦克 帮我把他搬到桌子底下
Mack, help me get him under the table, will ya?
好的
Okay.
我数三声
On my count.
得了吧 医生
Shut up, Doc.
拿个毯子
Get the blankets.
罗伯塔 听见我说话了吗
Roberta! Can you hear me?!
这次我一定要等他 查理
I have to wait for him this time, Charlie.
我欠他太多了
I owe him that much.
不 上帝啊 赶紧给我出来
No. No! Goddamn it! Come down right now!
这里不安全
It is not safe up here!
就像你说的那样
It's like you said.
我无法忘却
I can't start forgetting...
直到我知晓一切
until I know.
罗伯塔 求你别这样
Roberta, please don't do this.
很好 就是这样
Got it. That's it!
沃伦呢
Where's Warren?
她不会过来了
She's not coming.
什么
What?
什么叫她不会过来
She's not coming?
她在那会死掉的
She's gonna get killed out there.
必须到这儿来才行
She's got to get down here.
她不肯过来
She's not coming.
墨菲
Murphy.
不是吧
You kidding me?
你在和这玩意搞什么鬼
Quit screwing around with this thing.
走好
Mercy.
一万
10k.
没事
Okay.
坚持住
Hang on.
不要 不要
Oh no! Oh no!
天呐
Oh God.
我一直在等你
I waited for you.
好吧 挺好玩的
Well that was fun.
沃伦
Warren.
你看起来不太好 首领
You don't look so good, chief.
我要离开这里
I need to get out of here.
我现在就要离开这里
I need to get out of here now.
罗伯塔
Roberta!
嗨
Hey.
嗨 查理
Hi, Charlie.
你为什么不
Why didn't you...
你是怎么
How did you...
我本想回家
I tried to go home.
我成功了
I did.
但我还在这儿
But I'm still here.
谢天谢地你还在这儿
Thank God you are.
我还在这儿
I'm still here.
你真疯狂
You're crazy.
是的
Yeah.
你太疯狂了 你知道吗
You're crazy. You know that, right?
是有那么一点
A little bit, yeah.
沃伦
Warren.
噢 谢谢你
Oh. Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
天啊 要是看得到小家伙 我肯定会被吓死的
Man... If I see a munchkin, I'm gonna freak.
赶紧走吧
I need to go!
我不太喜欢你这模样
I'm not sure if I care for that look.
没人要你喜欢
Nobody ask to.
换了新的发型
New haircut.
墨菲还是没变
Same Murphy.
医生 谢谢
Hey, Doc. Thanks.
真的很谢谢你
Thank you truely
你有什么东西可以止痛吗
Do you have anything for the pain?
噢 我
Oh, I...
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
真希望我有
I wish I did.
好吧 见鬼
Oh, hell.
给你
Here.
慢点吃 这可是好东西
Take it easy on those, that's good stuff.
你们以后怎么办
Are you folks gonna be all right?
这附近有里克的家人
Rick's got family nearby.
我们打算去找他们
We're gonna keep looking for them.
不过还是谢谢了
But thanks.
谢谢你们做的一切
Thanks for everything.
什么
What?
你是对的 我应该回来的
You were right. I did need to come back.
就算我不知道安东尼发生了什么事
Even if I never know for sure what happened to Antoine,
我已经说过再见了
I said my goodbye.
我知道我现在还活着就很好
I know I'm okay with being here now.
和你一起就很好了
With you.
我也觉得这样挺好的
And I'm good with that too.
我一直都想试一下
I always wanted to do that.
我就知道
I could tell.
幸存者们 你们好
Survivors of the world, hello.
如果你们听到这个 那么恭喜 说明你们还活着
If you're hearing this, congrats. You're still alive.
你们是最凶残的生物
You are the baddest of the badasses.
人类 龙卷风 僵尸 都不是你们的对手
Fearing neither man nor twister nor living dead.
现在我摘下耳机 向你们致敬
My headset is off to you.